staying in the moment. They kept making
him snap it one more time on the
defensive side of the ball.
And I was proud of the way that we just,
you know, responded. We always talk
about, you know, let's let's not react,
let's respond.
And we don't have much time to be able
to enjoy it. You know, it's great to be
able to punch a ticket to the playoffs.
That's obviously always a goal is to be
able to give yourself a chance to play
extra games after that those 17 that
you're guaranteed, but I love this
football team.
And I'm excited, you know, about being
able to start the the preparation for
Seattle. Our guys are starting recovery
right now and
what help the challenge we have coming
up on Thursday. What was the adjustment
that you adjustment that you made coming
into the second half to get three
straight three and outs?
You know, [snorts] I think our guys
really just, you know, didn't give up
any loose yardage. I thought we knocked
out the run and I thought we were sticky
in coverage and we were able to apply
pressure to force him to progress past
some of their primary options. And so,
you know, just being able to earn the
right to be able to get the pen back in
your hand a little bit defensively.
That's an explosive offense. I mean,
they're leading the league in scoring.
They got playmakers all over the place.
Obviously, Jared does an excellent job
being able to distribute the ball, but I
thought we were able to affect and
influence that and just disrupt their
rhythm a little bit. We knocked out the
run all day and and that was a big
factor for them. They only have I think
it was 20 carries for 70 yards with how
explosive they are. So, it's really
solid job, you know, our coaches do a
great job of making those adjustments.
Give a ton of credit to them.
It was. Yeah. And so, we'll we'll see.
You know, I mean, you know, he was
optimistic talking to him. He knows his
body really well. They had an east and
west double. He split it and then, you
know, just kind of came up where he felt
it. So, we'll see what that means. I
can't imagine that's good for Thursday
with just the short amount of time, but
I certainly wouldn't rule him out quite
yet, but it didn't look good.
So, how how big was the difference
between those two touchdowns?
Yeah, it was huge. And And then I
thought we played complimentary
football, Dennis. That's the big thing
is is, you know, you start to just pull
away, get it to a 14-point game. I
thought our defense did a great job. You
know, I'd be interested to see what they
saw on the fourth down that they ended
up calling the penalty on. I thought
Forbes was in pretty good position.
You know, but ultimately, I'm not
responsible for making those calls, but
it was a great job by our defensive
staff anticipating, you know, the call
that they ended up getting to. And then
offensively, you know, churned out it
was great to be able to get one first
down right there. So, force them to use
their timeouts and you're giving it to
them with less than 20 seconds. You'd
like to be able to end with the ball,
but thought we did a great job at the
end, you know, being able to rally, make
the tackle and not allow them to snap it
again, but it was a great team win for
us. From 10 down to 10 out. Mhm.
I I just, you know, guys just playing
one snap at a time, Kurt. I think that
was the key and critical factor is, you
know, you don't you don't look at the
scoreboard, you just continue to try to
stack good plays, stay totally and
completely present, and over the course
of the game those things compound in a
good way if you're able to put it
together offensively, defensively, and
in the kicking game. And thought that's
what we were able to do. So, were you
able to see the intermediate middle
passing game cuz that seemed to really
get the offense on track?
Yeah, I think that's been a big factor
for us. You know, I you know, the big
one, you know, being able to hit a seam.
They had mixed up, you know, some of the
covered structures that they were
playing to some of the personnel groups
and that's where some of the voids and
vacancies, but I thought Matthew was on
point, you know, whether it was the
movement game,
whether it was some of the intermediate
stuff. And then I thought we were able
to push the ball down the field and and
take some opportunities. And I thought
guys were separating. They're a sticky
coverage outfit. And then when they did
play, you know, kind of vision zone
where their QB key ball out break,
thought we were able to make them pay.
And And that's a real credit to the
protection, Matthew playing on time and
in rhythm, and then guys being able to
get to their spots. Coach, with the win
Coach, with the win here,
you exercise some demons against
Detroit. You hold serve for the number
one position. You're also getting ready
to welcome another child into the world.
As you get ready to prepare for Seattle,
what's your process for
compartmentalizing I mean, how do I
answer that one, right, without you
really putting me in a You know,
obviously, the the family stuff is
What the hell kind of question is that
right there? I'll tell you what, it's
you know, here's the thing. I we talk
about being present all the time. I
think this group did a great job being
able to handle this first step of our
weekly rhythm and our challenge.
You know, obviously, we're praying for a
safe and healthy arrival of our second
little boy. That'll be awesome.
My wife is a total stud. You know, my
respect just watching and and getting an
up close and personal look at this. I
could never do this stuff. But but
there's a lot of love, there's a lot of
appreciation, and a lot of gratitude.
So, we'll pray for a safe and healthy
arrival. And And then I'll be stressed
out preparing for Seattle on a short
week, but it's good stress, you know, so
our guys will be ready to go. It's going
to be a great challenge and you know,
it's what you love about the NFL. The
offense looked sloppy early, dropped
snaps, missed missed throws, but then
they turned it on like a dime.
Yeah, you know, and I think the key
thing was I thought even if even when we
were just a tick off, we were still able
to make some big conversions on some of
the fourth downs, you know, where you
might have missed something that we're
accustomed to be able to execute at a
high clip, but we were able to overcome
some of them. Not all of them, but the
majority of them to still be able to get
some points.
You know, only punted that one time in
the first half and then I obviously at
the end of the game, but I just think
our guys, you know, just play the next
snap. Do the next right thing. If it
doesn't go down, you know, sometimes
you're not always going to physically
execute the way that you want, but what
can you do other than just do the next
right thing? And that's what I thought
our guys did. Obviously, Matthew got
really hot. I thought he was seeing the
field really well. I had total command.
We were in and out of some different
personnel groupings and I thought a lot
of guys got involved. I thought our line
was excellent. You know, that's a real
rush outfit. We were able to be
efficient enough in the run game to be
able to keep them at bay. And thought
Matthew was excellent being able to keep
the ball on play even after a couple,
you know, things that you mentioned from
us just collectively offensively, myself
included, where we could be better, but
we were able to overcome it.
Yeah, it was honestly just a just a
change of mind. I felt comfortable using
a timeout right there and
had a play that we liked and you know,
that's on me. You know, that that whole
sequence, you know, that that was my
fault there. What type of tone did that
type of aggressive decision make in
there and then going for points at the
end of the second quarter second half? I
thought it was big, Adam. You know, and
and guys just delivered on their
opportunities. You know, what our job is
as coaches is try to make decisions that
set our players up for successful
outcomes. They're the ones that bring it
to life. They deserve all the all the
credit in the world.
You know, but there are situations and
you know, circumstances where you say,
"Man, I got a lot of confidence in our
group. Let's go execute." You knew that
it was going to be, you know, that kind
of game where there was some good back
and forth and you needed to be able to
know that, you know, points were going
to be really important for us. And And
our guys delivered in a big way. So,
knowing what's ahead, how much do you
consider the short week during the game?
Like, I need to do this. Oh, no, not at
all. You know, I mean, that's too there
it's too back and forth. You know, you
can't afford to do that. You have to be
able to take care of your business.
You know, if we were able to establish a
lead and and do those things, then
that's different, but that wasn't the
case. That thing came all the way down
to the wire. They're too explosive
offensively. And shoot, you're still
till that clock hits zero, you know, I'm
not feeling great, but I did love the
way that our guys handled, you know, the
pressure moments at the end. DK, the
last one. Who got hit in his 100%
receptions tonight? Can you speak to the
fact that he's a stud player?
Yeah, he's unbelievable. I mean, the guy
just produces. He's so tough. You know,
there's a couple times where he just
drags guys with him where you're saying,
"Just get down so you don't leave
yourself." I thought he got hit in the
back of the head. He was just cramping
on the one that he caught over the
middle before he ended up hitting Colby
for the touchdown, but he's a stud. He
epitomizes everything that we want to be
about as do so many of our players, but
it's like Pac-Man. He just eats up yards
and catches. And
you know, but he is so tough. Go ahead,
you like that one, huh? All right. But
he's he's he's special. He's a special
competitor, special player. He loves the
game. Our players, they love playing
together. They love enjoying these
challenges. And Thursday represents
another one and we got to be ready to
go.
All right. Thank you, guys.
>> Mhm.
>> Lot of folks in here. Go ahead. Um, how
big was that drive at the end of the
half where you made that play? Yeah, it
was a big one. Uh, right before that I
was like, man, let's go steal three. You
know, I told the guys I was like, let's
go steal three points. See what happens
and uh
you know, first only got the got the uh
little completion over the back over the
ball and then um
Sean called the great when it was the
same one I was thinking. I was like,
please go to this. And he thought it and
thought the same thing. And then uh you
know, playing like a super prevent
defense, I tried to just
um you know, move the post player and
give uh Puka as much space as he could
um to do his thing and he did and
obviously made a great play and got it
down in there and
um getting three there is big. Being
able to come back in the second half and
and tie it up, you know, is is a big
one.
How's it feel to
clinch a playoff spot here on the field
after you know, the last couple years
you needed some help to
Uh it feels good, you know, to be honest
with you, we didn't talk about it for
one second this week. Um
you know, just another opponent, another
really good opponent we had to play you
know, at our place and um
you know, we knew it was going to be a
tough one so, but you know, great to
great accomplishment, lot more lot more
football to be played.
What were you thinking when Sean went
for it on those two fourth downs earlier
in the game?
Yeah, you know, I was excited. You know,
obviously we had some chances on some
third downs, didn't get it done and and
um but I thought we you know, clutched
up, made some plays on fourth down.
Um you know, and and was able to get
some points out of it so um you know,
playing a good offense um you know, like
Detroit has, you know, you got to stay
with them. We we obviously we moved it
good in the first half. Had the
turnover, you know, Aiden made a great
play. Looked like he was primary
receiver on the damn play.
Um
so hell of a play and then made me look
silly in space. So uh but uh
yeah, I mean, we moved it good and you
know, good enough to to put points up.
Obviously didn't um you know, connect on
a couple there to uh to
you know, get the touchdowns that we
needed, but um you know, those fourth
downs were big. If you do get those
fourth down plays, just what does it
mean to you to have a player like Puka
where the defense knows that's likely
where you might go and yet he's still
able to make a catch? Yeah, he did a
great job. Um you know, obviously caught
the one versus a mask. You know, they're
trying to show me man coverage and then
popped out into a Tampa you know, Tampa
two prevent, you know, quick defense and
Puka did a nice job settling in a hole
there and I just tried to put it on him
and he did a great job falling forward.
And the next one showed us the man look,
stayed man and and Puka did a nice job
winning and and then catching it to at
the catch point. Matthew, how did you
guys Kobe Parkinson get his fourth
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean I've I've you know had a
blast getting to work with him, watching
him, you know, you know, continue to get
better as a football player is awesome.
I think he's playing as good a football
as he probably ever has.
Um
Uh you know, it's a credit to the other
guys in that room, the coach in that
room. They do a hell of a job of of, you
know, pulling for each other. That's the
cool part about that group, man. We got
a bunch of guys in there that are all
pulling for each other's success and you
never know whose day it's going to be.
Um Colby obviously, you know, made some
plays today on the, you know, the deep
ball and then
great on third down on one I had to
progress to him and did a great job of
making a tough catch. Um but I thought
all those guys played well today, um but
happy for Colby and his success.
Um you know, I
obviously unfortunate to turn the ball
over early in the game, which is, you
know, kind of a momentum killer, but you
know, I thought um you know, that's that
drive right before half was nice um to
get three and then come out and then,
you know, just play a really consistent
steady second half.
Um and I thought our defense played
great in the second half, too, which was
awesome.
Yeah, I mean
um
there's still plenty of plays I want
back and and that we could clean up. So,
uh you know, I'm not going to put a
you know, a a metric on it for us. I
just want us to continue to keep working
hard, keep playing and I know that's
what we will do. Um you know, we got the
right group group of guys that
you know, all we want to do is go to
work and find a way to be better and and
continue to find ways to win football
games as a team.
Um it's it's a fun group right now, but
uh you know, we we understand that
there's more out there for us.
Yeah, I mean obviously an outstanding
football player, a huge part of our
offense, a guy that's um you know, put
it in the in the end zone a bunch for us
this year and and so,
um you know, that'll be a tough one. I I
I don't know the extent of it. Didn't
look like it was a a good one. So,
uh feel so so tough for him. He's been
he's been a warrior for us all year
really to be honest with you. Um playing
out there for us. So, um
we'll see. I got a lot of faith and
trust in the other guys that we have in
our locker room and and our coaching
staff to put us in a great position to
go out there, let our
you know, let our play do the talking
and just go play.
Physically. Um just trying to
you know, I mean I don't even know how
many hours we got till we play again,
but yeah, I mean that's the hardest
part. Um
you know, obviously big time opponent,
going on the road, at their place, uh
difficult, you know, scheme, bunch of
great players on that side. So,
it'll be a huge challenge whether we're
playing Sunday, Monday, Thursday,
whatever day of the week.
Um but just trying to get our bodies
turned over and and um you know, be as
fresh as we can on Thursday.
Yeah, I mean it's a it's a huge part of
it, you know, and and we spend a lot of
time talking about it, spend a lot of
time thinking about it, communicating
constantly on, you know, how we think
the rhythm of the game is going to go,
how we're going to start the game, how
we think
you know, series are going to go in in
the game. You know, he comes over, pops
to me on the bench, I'm talking to him,
he's talking to me. Um you know, and so
I I love love getting to play
quarterback when he's calling plays. He
did a hell of a job today and and um
just happy that like we always are, you
know, in in sync and and moving in the
right direction.
Cool. Thanks.
>> Good.
Yeah, I didn't even realize it. Um
we never talked about that this week. It
was all about, you know, figuring out a
way to go and and pick up a W and then
being ready to move forward again this
week and pick up another W. So, it's
definitely really cool. Um I mean, it's
all about getting into the fight at the
end of the year and uh crazy stuff
happens. It's just about getting there
and so it's awesome to know that we
clinched that and we're continuing to
just take it week by week. Like I said,
we we had no clue that we clinched it.
Um but super cool, for sure. Did you not
talk about it because that's generally
what you don't do anyway, or is it the
goal is not that?
Well, I mean, obviously our goal is to
is to go out each and every week and
come away with a W. Um and we know what
this team is capable of. Uh but yeah, it
wasn't like we had to have a conscious
focus of let's not talk about what's at
stake. It's just we don't really like
obviously you care about getting there,
but we're not focused on the future.
We're not focused on things that are so
far um in advance. We're just focused on
each and every day and that's been
giving us good results. So, I think
we're going to continue to do that. What
did Justin say to you guys at halftime
to get Jared out of his
funk for three and out after, you know,
Detroit doesn't find the first half?
Yeah, um one of the biggest things was
coach kind of came in and gave us the
green light. Uh they were being able to
get us in big personnels and and drop
some some deep shots down. Um and you
know, we're playing the run. Obviously,
Gibbs is a super talented running back,
elite. Um and if you give him any
creases, he's going to expose you. Uh
but we decided, you know, coming out of
half, play fast, get the green light. Uh
if it looks like pass, if it smells like
pass, go get after it. Um and so we're
able to get him off the spot, uh get to
affect him a little bit, and then we
started to feel like, you know, this is
Rams defense. This is our ball, the way
that we know how to play. Um so, super
proud of that second half effort, for
sure. What does that feel like when
you're playing complimentary ball, able
to go
20 to 0 run as a team?
Yeah, you feel unstoppable.
Um we kind of got a taste of our own
medicine in a sense when uh they got the
pick and then they came down and scored
and I was like, "Wow, like this is what
it feels like when we're doing that to
other teams. So, let's figure out a way
uh to to go and do that." And that's
exactly what happened coming out of the
half, uh being being able to get stops,
being able to go down and get
touchdowns. You you feel on top of the
world. It's like we're rolling. We have
our breath. Uh you know, we we have the
momentum. Um it's an incredible feeling.
So, that's what ultimately the goal is.
Obviously, there's sometimes like in the
first half, offense had to pick us up
defensively. Uh but when we're both
firing on all cylinders, man, you you
put on the foot on the gas and you leave
people behind.
It was awesome. Um I think again, coming
out of second half, I was able to get in
that mindset of got the green light. You
know, if I if I feel pass, smell pass,
like just go get active. So, the play
before, uh was able to get a pressure
because of that mentality. And then you
come back in the next play, it just
something feels different. It feels like
pass, for sure. Um so, to be able to set
up our moves. Um and then a huge credit
to the three other guys as well, rushing
with me. Uh a lot of times people have
quick wins and they won't result in
sacks, but because of the way that we
collapse the pocket um and that we owned
all four edges of the quarterback, I was
able to to come away with the sack. So,
uh super super proud of that and and I'm
looking forward to continuing it. Talk
about the opportunity for the defense as
well as when you guys talk about just
taking it game by game, knowing how good
you are, but not getting too
overconfident and staying in the
Yeah, I mean, all of our guys, [snorts]
for lack of better terms, are built
different. I mean, if you just look at
our front, there's four of us guys who
have gotten it out of the mud,
guys who have, you know, BY going to
JUCO, Verse going to Albany, being in
the CAA with me, me walking on at
Richmond, Fist going to Western
Michigan. And now we transfer up, get
the opportunity to go and better
ourselves. I mean, we're hungry. Um at
the end of the day, that's the best way
I can describe this defense. And that
doesn't just go for our front, that goes
for everybody. We all have something to
prove. Um and we're just enjoying,
honestly, every opportunity we get to go
and play together. We didn't put out,
you know, our our best effort on the on
the first half, but each and every
opportunity you have, I mean, we've been
trying to take advantage of it. The
offense had our backs. We were able to
come up big in the second half. And man,
like you just I love [snorts] being able
to be a part of that group because
whatever happens, we're never out of the
fight. Whatever happens, we're going to
keep scrapping. We're hungry. We're
built different. Coach, in the third
quarter, called you third quarter,
Fiskie injured his ankle. I see you walk
over to the trainer table to to go check
on him. And
>> Yeah, I mean first of all just the the
relationship that I have with him the
relationship that I have with all of my
guys in the D-line room. I mean that was
the first thing that was on my mind.
Yeah, we got off the field but I saw him
limp off and I know he's had his battle
with injuries before as well. I remember
last year in the Eagles game too and so
I just wanted to check on him check how
he was feeling check how his mental was.
He gave me the thumbs up you know he
felt fine and so was able to move on
from there but that's my brother. That's
the most important thing is making sure
we're all good to go for sure.
Yeah, I mean I think obviously Seattle
has a very tough crowd as well. I'm sure
it's going to be cold. I haven't looked
at the weather
but you just know Seattle late in the
season night game
and then obviously it's a very talented
team. We've been toe-to-toe.
We're leading the NFC West right now but
they've been right on our tail so
um
there's a lot of challenges and we're
going to get in the film and kind of
look at all of you know what we need to
do and and address it
but I'm so excited. The way that these
guys in this locker room are built
the way that we handle adversity the way
that whatever happens whatever is thrown
at us we handle it the right way. The
mental wiring of okay it doesn't matter
if it's a short week or a long week.
We're going to make sure that we go and
prepare the right way so that we can put
out our best work on Saturday Sunday
Thursday Monday it doesn't matter. So
really in these weeks I really feel like
we have an advantage because we're made
of the right stuff. I'm sure there's
other teams that are made of some some
good stuff too but we're built the right
way and I hope we show it.
It came from the DC came from Shula and
also came from our position coach.
Came from Giff as well. It was more so
of you know we've been doing a really
good job at the run but there's a lot of
times where we're getting called on
blocks and when it was a deep developing
play action pass you kind of play the
run you're looking around all of a
sudden now you're already engulfed and
so
we have you know our tails film study
preparation also allows us to have
certain tails and when something goes a
little bit different than what you're
expecting off of film you're able to
play faster and then certainly getting
the green light from DC from Shula and
getting it from Giff helps you to play
faster as well.
Appreciate you guys.
Hello everyone.
Doing great. How are you guys?
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, well honestly I mean we we knew
that we're going to come out strong in
the third quarter but the defense played
so amazing that second half so
they really just allowed that third
quarter to be a shut out like
like we talked about at halftime and
played really well offensively too which
was
always psyched with the run game and you
know goes from there.
Yeah, I think getting different
personnel groups out there definitely
helps.
I mean Shawn and the offensive staff do
such great job just scheming up
different looks.
There'll be plays in that don't stall
during during meetings and say hey we're
looking at it for this look and they'll
line up and be like oh this is exactly
what we designed it for and it's pretty
cool I just having so much trust in the
in the coaching staff and that they
trust me too.
Yeah, I mean it's business as usual with
him. He is
the ultimate pro such a stud and
none of us ever flinch if any any mishap
happens which is very rare especially
this season so
we have total confidence in him and we
responded the right way as a team too.
Yeah, it's it's a lot of fun. That's for
sure but I always talk about the group
as a whole. Our tight end room is
amazing. We do a great job picking each
other up helping each other out with the
different looks like I wouldn't be doing
this without Davis doing what he's doing
Ferg doing what he's doing Nick Vannett
Tyler Higbee when he's healthy like it
all starts as a group and I'm super
thankful for those guys and
it could be any one of us any week so
thankful for those guys.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, I I mean I love the install
meetings now that's for sure. When we
when we go through all of 13 stuff it's
a lot of fun and getting out there with
those guys is just great cuz we're able
to trust each other we're we can bounce
ideas off each other for what whatever
the defense presenting.
So it's a lot of fun and it's cool that
we are all contributing so much to
helping this team win too.
Yeah, I mean I sorry I made you guys
wait but it starts with recovery right
after the game we're doing massages cold
tub hot tub all that stuff and
the main thing is just getting your body
back and
making sure we're ready to go out there
and play fast on Thursday.
Definitely. I mean that four-day
turnarounds it's very quick so making
sure your body's ready to go and the
coaches will put together a great great
plan for us and we'll see what we get on
Thursday.
Yeah, I mean Lumen they have great fans.
I don't think the short week necessarily
adds any anything to that maybe the
night game just for the environment.
It'll be a really fun environment
looking forward to it. Obviously spent a
lot of time up there my first four years
so excited to go back and you know get
the win.
I felt like I caught it.
>> [laughter]
>> I I thought there's no doubt I caught
it. I know the defender he's able to get
his hand in there but I thought I was
able to keep the ball
off the ground in that instance and
yeah I mean Matthew just threw an
amazing ball and fun that he trusted me
with that one. Kobe, as a position
group, you guys are like a Swiss Army
knife.
Is there a nickname that you guys have
amongst one another for yourselves? No,
but we should come up with one. That's a
good idea. You got any ideas? I'll
I'll get back to All right. All right.
Get back to me. Kobe,
obviously more work to be done, but just
what's it mean to
earn the opportunity to reach playoffs?
Yeah, I mean that's what you play for
every year, right? Is an opportunity to
playoffs. All you need is your foot in
the door. Obviously, we're going to go
out there though these last three weeks
and try to secure a good seeding and all
that, but
we are
built for built for it. That's what
Sean's been saying all season. We're
built for it and we're excited for what
the playoffs might bring, but we got
Seahawks coming up in a few days, so
we're focused on that.
All right, coach. Thank you. All right.
Thank you guys. God bless.
Kyren, how does it feel to clinch a
playoff spot on the road? Uh it feels
great. Um you know, this is obviously I
didn't know this was a
a chance that we could do that today,
but you know, it makes that win even
much more better. And for me it was
honestly like this is the my third time
playing the Detroit Lions and my first
time beating them. Um so for me we we
clinched the playoffs, but we all have
also been a team that has, you know,
shown shown us a defeat twice for me
twice in a row, so
um it's even more even more of a
blessing to be able to get that win and
get into the playoffs, too. It seems
like all the guys didn't know that you
were going to clinch the spot. Yeah. How
much of that is that's just the way you
guys are brought into the system or
there's a bigger goal out there anyway?
I think it's a little bit of both. You
know, we don't talk about those type of
things. You know, we don't talk about
clinching the playoffs. We don't talk
about, you know, hopefully getting to
the Super Bowl. We don't do none of
that. We just focus on each and every
single day. Um today's Sunday. We're
going to move on from whatever
happened today from this from the game
and then continue to keep getting
better. I think that's been the the
motto or the you know, the focus
throughout this whole year is just
continue to keep getting better after
each and every single game and not
looking at the the so-called results,
but more of just like how can we
improve? And so to me and this team we I
don't think we've ever heard anybody
talk about any playoffs or anything like
that. It's just consistently getting
better even every day. Kyren, can you
talk about the progress that you're
making with Blake
too?
>> Yeah.
Oh yeah. I think it's that's going to be
something in the in the near future
that's going to really take the league
by storm. And we're we're doing it now
in a way that, you know, it was leading
us up for this post season. So I think
it's really great how Blake and I are
able to you know, get those carries and
feed off each other and you know, just
show the difference the defense two
different things, you know, and it
allows us to stay fresh throughout the
whole game and you know, create more
explosives throughout the first quarter
into the fourth quarter. So
being able to be with Blake and do the
things that we do is amazing. It's a
blessing and we're going to continue to
keep getting better. And how much do you
think [clears throat] of saving your
body over the over the long haul as well
by doing that? Um you know, obviously
that is I guess the main focus of doing
something like that, but for me it's
more of being able to see, you know, a
superstar like Blake to succeed. You
know, he obviously he's done what he's
done his whole life and you being able
to get to the league and he's still
doing those type of things to me it's
it's amazing and you know, I'm super
happy for the things that he's doing cuz
he's showing the world what we already
obviously we already know.
Um but and it's also saving us, too. So
for me it's just a blessing all around.
Yeah.
Those are like confidence builders. Like
those I think as a coach like you go out
there and you instill that confidence in
your guys. I think I don't know what the
fourth down was what fourth and 10?
Fourth and 12?
Fourth and eight. Exactly. Like those
are situations we're punting the ball or
most teams are punting the ball. I don't
even say we. Most teams are punting the
ball.
But we're different, you know. I think
coach McVay has
has shown that throughout the season and
even in practice we get in those
situations of where, you know, run that
run that rep back. Run that rep back
again. We didn't get it right the first
time. Let's do it again. Let's let's get
this stuff right. And so to me that's
just all about execution, confidence and
you know, him just trusting in his
players.
You guys go for a lot of fourth downs.
Puka's coming up with a catch and run in
the last few weeks. What is the feeling
as an offense? What what kind of lift do
you get out of it? Can't stop us.
You can't stop us. You know where the
ball's going. You still can't stop us.
Like for me that's just it's it's so
cool seeing being out there on the field
and you know, with great guys like Puka
and Demarcus and all the tight ends and
offensive lineman and it's fourth down.
They think they got us and then we you
know, we get the first down. So to me
that feeling is like haha, you can't
stop us. We're going to keep doing what
we're doing, but
I think that's just also goes to the
execution of the guys, you know, being
able to keep Matthew up, Puka being able
to run a great route and Matthew being
able to deliver a great ball. So you
know, all around team sport, but you
know, those those right there are
confidence builders. I was curious if I
got to talk to Ronnie and he mentioned
how the running back room really
encourages and helps throughout the
week. Can you speak to how you guys as
just the running
>> Yeah.
like
help yourselves get to where you are?
>> Yeah. I think that starts I mean I don't
think I know that starts with coach G.
You know, he's the type of coach that
like we're a family. You know, this
running back room is a family and we all
we do things together. You know, we eat
breakfast together. We go to
walk-throughs together. We do a lot of
things together. We're always hanging
out. And that just speaks about the the
camaraderie of this team. You know, I I
think a lot of people on this in this
league or in this team like you don't
experience those type of things, but on
this team it's different. You know, we
don't just hang out as position groups.
We also hang out as, you know, a whole
team and stuff like that. So I think our
running back room creates a bond that
allows the team to be able to see like
man, we're all family. And so shout out
to coach Jean to the in the guys in that
in that running back room to make it
fun. I hope you got a couple more here.
How scary is it to lose Demarcus the way
you did and Puka have to leave not too
much later and a short week? Yeah.
I'm I don't I'm not scared. I got
confidence. I got faith in
whether, you know, Demarcus is out there
or Puka's out there. Whoever it is, I
know the job's going to get done. And
you know, that's just kind of the the
overall mindset of this team like the
next man up kind of mentality, but you
know, we're praying for Demarcus.
Obviously, Puka's okay, but praying for
Demarcus and hoping that he has a speedy
recovery and hoping that it's nothing
serious, but whoever it is that's going
to step up whether it's Mumph, whether
it's Xavier Smith, man, I'm excited.
It's going to be a show. I one thing
that we've heard is you guys are built
for this. Heck yeah. Has that been a
theme from the beginning of the season?
Mhm.
From training camp. Okay. From training
camp. I think that's might have been the
first thing coach McVay told us we're
built for it. Whatever that is. Whatever
it is. Adversity, the good, the bad, the
ugly, the indifferent. We're built for
it. You know, coach McVay always says
that the enemy has a say so. And I think
that allows us to know that we're built
for it cuz we're they're going to have
they're going to punch us in the mouth.
You know, this is a it's a hard fought
game.
But we continue to keep punching and we
continue to keep just being who we are,
believing in ourselves and we're built
for it. And that's really a motto that
we all stand on. Kyren, there's a lot of
you were talking about just the running
back room and how close that you guys
are. How do you see the styles Yeah. You
all have a very individualized style.
How do you how do you see all that
coming together to compliment one
another? Um I think it just comes with
precision on each play depending on what
play it is. You know, I think um duos
and those are the downhill runs. You got
to be patient. You got to be able to
have great vision, great burst and you
know, being able to hit the hit those
holes when they're there.
And then the outside zone and mid zones
is what we do. I just honestly think we
we all kind of do something similar, but
in a different way.
For me I know my my whole focus is, you
know, being able to be efficient. You
know, stay ahead of the chains, be able
to fall forward and you know, get those
positive yards. Get us get us ahead of
chains so that when you know, coach
McVay goes back to the play call he sees
a second and four instead of a second
and eight or something like that. So for
me I think that plays off into you know,
what Blake does. Blake is a also a great
great efficient back, but he also has
the ability and that juice to be able to
make you miss and turn the corner. And
so
I honestly think that we like I said
earlier, we just feed off each other. I
don't think there's one specific thing
that we both do is is we're just out
there hooping. That's why I'm going to
piggyback off that. Give them Montgomery
and his two That's what everyone talks
about and your defense scheme for them
you know, in the first half today, but
you and Blake quietly under the radar
Yeah. you know, you're on two-headed
monster statistically last few weeks. So
why should opponents, you know, not take
you and Blake for granted? They can do
what they want to do.
Cuz Blake and I honestly we know what
it's about and we know what we're going
to do. Like I said, that we we are two
competitive running backs who got juice
to go make things happen.
And whether you want to call us a you
know, the number one duo or whatever we
we land at, you know, we have that
belief and confidence that we are the
best running back duo in the league and
like I told in earlier it's going to be
shown in the near future. And so as long
as we keep working and keep doing what
we're doing,
everybody will see.
Appreciate you guys. God bless.
>> What's up everybody? Stu?
Boger check.
Chase Chase said I had a few seconds to
say whatever I wanted. So I'm going to
take this opportunity to say
sorry for making you guys wait, but my
mom and I do have a dinner reservation.
So if we could be
my mom and Akua is waiting for me.
I love this game of football and knowing
that how important it is to for this
game and everything everybody sacrifice
and in this crunch time moment there's
no place I'd rather be than out there on
the field with those guys.
I'm like yeah, I think it's more of a
the Pac-Man when he eats the big ones
and I'm like everybody's the ghost. Like
I'm trying to run through everybody. So
I I like that. [laughter]
>> [snorts]
[snorts]
>> It was the game that was coming up for
this weekend with the mindset and the
mentality that we've been carrying
throughout week to week. We were super
excited cuz these guys were coming into
our town and I know the last time I
played them I had an injury so I wasn't
able to finish and be out there with the
guys. So this is one I was excited go
out there and obviously when I get to
play family going against Penei so you
got to make sure you have a good
showing. So
>> [laughter]
>> It is still Sunday. So I'm like I'm
on the process of recovery, but it's
another one to get to go chance to see
those boys and if Cooper Kupp's going to
be there I'll definitely be there.
I'm sure there was some some extra long
exhales on the sideline, but it'll be a
a great opportunity for us to to
challenge ourselves immensely and
physically prepare for this week on on a
short week and I know our training staff
is is going to get a good night's rest
cuz we're going to need them.
>> [snorts]
>> I wasn't a dark place after I dropped
that first one. I was like man that one
really hurt. I'm like I thought about
that one getting released and coach
Shawn was definitely mad.
Had a choice words for me after that
one, but it feels fine. I have so much
trust and confidence in number nine and
I know he feels the same. So the the
ability to put my foot in the ground and
trust where that placement is going to
be
I think is something that I don't take
for granted every Sunday and the reps
that we get through the week they pay
off out here.
I think that's football at its finest. I
think it's fun. We talk so much about
our run game and
I love that and the ability to be like
hey everybody
man-on-man you know exactly where we're
about to hand this ball off. So and when
it's my opportunity to make those plays
it's even more fun.
Trusting that every spot that everybody
else is going to do the job and then it
just leaving it up to me and to be able
to come down with that ball. I knew I
owed nine one. So it was fun.
I think it's huge. I it shows how much
he trusts us and the the command that he
has
in our offense, but then also how much
the command of number nine and trusting
that he's going to make the right
decision even in some of those those
third down conversions late in the game
going to Tay. So it just made it fun.
When the opportunity I know in the our
wide receiver room we live for those
moments. We want the plays to come to us
because we we love that challenge.
I think it'll take all 11 as it does
every single week, but I think it'll be
a great opportunity for the young guys
and especially
month
who's been behind him watching and is
somebody that we feel like is
Tay's apprentice. So it'll be it'll be
fun for him to be able to get those
extra reps during practice, but then
also
to do everything we can to make sure
number 17 has an opportunity to be out
there.
I think there's definitely some more
head slaps that's going on, but I know I
I I
I love that and I think there is a
moment where everybody gets to flex and
and there's no there's no better
feeling. I know that you guys have seen
me get a penalty for that, but I think
it's fun when everybody we get back in
the huddle and everybody you you you
show your muscles off and knowing that
we're about to do the same thing in the
next play. Hooker 211 and three teams
Thursday night short week. I mean, how
much fun is this? I mean,
it's such an important game.
I continue to say it every weekend
before the games. I I thank the Lord for
the blessing that it is that I have to
play this game of football and the
opportunity I get to play out here with
these guys. We have a a special group
here and there's no better moment than
this Thursday coming up. Yeah, like you
said, the two teams who have been
playing really great football and it'll
be another opportunity for it to show
what we've been doing.
Thank you guys.